[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Let me start with you, if I can, George Howell, what is the situation in Buffalo?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "if", "I", "can", ",", "George", "Howell", ",", "what", "is", "the", "situation", "in", "Buffalo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Piers, so we are just now starting to see the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "so", "we", "are", "just", "now", "starting", "to", "see", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Howell"], "LOCATION": ["Buffalo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Pittsburgh International Airport"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Are the -- Is the airport operating properly?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "--", "Is", "the", "airport", "operating", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "Well, Piers, just a short while ago, I actually got off the phone with an official with the Pittsburgh International Airport and they said to me that today and right now, actually, all operations are normal that this is essentially, this rain fall that's happening, this is standard operating procedure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "just", "a", "short", "while", "ago", ",", "I", "actually", "got", "off", "the", "phone", "with", "an", "official", "with", "the", "Pittsburgh", "International", "Airport", "and", "they", "said", "to", "me", "that", "today", "and", "right", "now", ",", "actually", ",", "all", "operations", "are", "normal", "that", "this", "is", "essentially", ",", "this", "rain", "fall", "that", "'s", "happening", ",", "this", "is", "standard", "operating", "procedure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Shannon, thank you very much indeed.", "answer_tokens": ["Shannon", ",", "thank", "you", "very", "much", "indeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What's the latest?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "latest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well this definitely the busiest time at the world's busiest airport.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "this", "definitely", "the", "busiest", "time", "at", "the", "world", "'s", "busiest", "airport", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Is that an accurate assessment?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "accurate", "assessment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Macy", "Macy"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "When is it going to be move pretty well back to normal weather wise?", "question_tokens": ["When", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "move", "pretty", "well", "back", "to", "normal", "weather", "wise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "YERS: You know if we get through the Macy's Day parade with the balloons up we're just talking about that in the last hour 34 miles per hour and the Macy's Day parade will be to cut off the balloons, the big floats, the big snoopies can't fly around.", "answer_tokens": ["YERS", ":", "You", "know", "if", "we", "get", "through", "the", "Macy", "'s", "Day", "parade", "with", "the", "balloons", "up", "we", "'re", "just", "talking", "about", "that", "in", "the", "last", "hour", "34", "miles", "per", "hour", "and", "the", "Macy", "'s", "Day", "parade", "will", "be", "to", "cut", "off", "the", "balloons", ",", "the", "big", "floats", ",", "the", "big", "snoopies", "ca", "n't", "fly", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "So, it's just really about tomorrow isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "really", "about", "tomorrow", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Yup.", "answer_tokens": ["Yup", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Gary, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Gary", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Good to see you again, man.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "see", "you", "again", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Good to see you.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "see", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "So how do we all basically save money while spending a fortune on Black Friday?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "do", "we", "all", "basically", "save", "money", "while", "spending", "a", "fortune", "on", "Black", "Friday", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "You know, if we start following these retail brands on Facebook, Twitter I think the one place to really start paying attention to is Pinterest and Instagram are emerging as well.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "if", "we", "start", "following", "these", "retail", "brands", "on", "Facebook", ",", "Twitter", "I", "think", "the", "one", "place", "to", "really", "start", "paying", "attention", "to", "is", "Pinterest", "and", "Instagram", "are", "emerging", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "ORGAN: Is this now that the biggest social media meets commercial shopping day that America has?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "this", "now", "that", "the", "biggest", "social", "media", "meets", "commercial", "shopping", "day", "that", "America", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "NNS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "This is brilliance.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "brilliance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "How many followers have you got now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "followers", "have", "you", "got", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Over a million now.", "answer_tokens": ["Over", "a", "million", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Walmart"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What is the key message that you want people to take away from this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "key", "message", "that", "you", "want", "people", "to", "take", "away", "from", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "The key message is whether it's this show or Walmart or Gap or anybody in the world that has something to convert that if you don't give, give, give, you can't go in for the ask.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "key", "message", "is", "whether", "it", "'s", "this", "show", "or", "Walmart", "or", "Gap", "or", "anybody", "in", "the", "world", "that", "has", "something", "to", "convert", "that", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "give", ",", "give", ",", "give", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "go", "in", "for", "the", "ask", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Austin", "Texas", "Columbus", "Ohio", "San Francisco", "New York"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What did you make in the whole ObamaCare Fiasco in particularly the technological failings that led to the rollout's biggest disaster, I mean, did they just get it completely wrong and who they source this too and how they did it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "in", "the", "whole", "ObamaCare", "Fiasco", "in", "particularly", "the", "technological", "failings", "that", "led", "to", "the", "rollout", "'s", "biggest", "disaster", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "did", "they", "just", "get", "it", "completely", "wrong", "and", "who", "they", "source", "this", "too", "and", "how", "they", "did", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I'm not knowledgeable enough to talk about the actual ObamaCare but from a tax standpoint, this is classic big government, same way I look at big corporate America, spent a lot of money and lack of execution, there's a bunch of entrepreneurs in Austin, Texas or in Columbus, Ohio or at San Francisco, (inaudible) New York, a small group of entrepreneurs that could have executed that technology for one 100 in the price.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "knowledgeable", "enough", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "actual", "ObamaCare", "but", "from", "a", "tax", "standpoint", ",", "this", "is", "classic", "big", "government", ",", "same", "way", "I", "look", "at", "big", "corporate", "America", ",", "spent", "a", "lot", "of", "money", "and", "lack", "of", "execution", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "bunch", "of", "entrepreneurs", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "or", "in", "Columbus", ",", "Ohio", "or", "at", "San", "Francisco", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", "New", "York", ",", "a", "small", "group", "of", "entrepreneurs", "that", "could", "have", "executed", "that", "technology", "for", "one", "100", "in", "the", "price", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Green"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Is he right Gary?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "right", "Gary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Yes, and he's partner in crime who's really leading that charge Joe Green, that whole movement is 100 percent right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "partner", "in", "crime", "who", "'s", "really", "leading", "that", "charge", "Joe", "Green", ",", "that", "whole", "movement", "is", "100", "percent", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "But can Hollywood just shut its eyes and ignore its own culpability or responsibility?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "Hollywood", "just", "shut", "its", "eyes", "and", "ignore", "its", "own", "culpability", "or", "responsibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, I think Obama coming and speaking is a good thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "Obama", "coming", "and", "speaking", "is", "a", "good", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Did you have that kind of internal editorial debate about ever using weapons in luxury that kind of thing there?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "that", "kind", "of", "internal", "editorial", "debate", "about", "ever", "using", "weapons", "in", "luxury", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "I think there's always a debate about what goes into the issue and how far are you push and getting behind that decision of why you would print a certain image or not or holding back.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "always", "a", "debate", "about", "what", "goes", "into", "the", "issue", "and", "how", "far", "are", "you", "push", "and", "getting", "behind", "that", "decision", "of", "why", "you", "would", "print", "a", "certain", "image", "or", "not", "or", "holding", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "That young kids in America are being pumped with more gun violence imagery than fully pledged adults?", "question_tokens": ["That", "young", "kids", "in", "America", "are", "being", "pumped", "with", "more", "gun", "violence", "imagery", "than", "fully", "pledged", "adults", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, I think it's -- I mean you look at \"Grand Theft Auto\", it made 800 million the first day it was released.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "mean", "you", "look", "at", "``", "Grand", "Theft", "Auto", "''", ",", "it", "made", "800", "million", "the", "first", "day", "it", "was", "released", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Was Hollywood pleased to see President Obama or has the -- has the warmth and joy is original ascension to great power abated over the years?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "Hollywood", "pleased", "to", "see", "President", "Obama", "or", "has", "the", "--", "has", "the", "warmth", "and", "joy", "is", "original", "ascension", "to", "great", "power", "abated", "over", "the", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Well, judging -- I don't know if you were out about L.A. today but judging by the traffic, I think Hollywood ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "judging", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "were", "out", "about", "L.A.", "today", "but", "judging", "by", "the", "traffic", ",", "I", "think", "Hollywood", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Do you think that his bubbles actually burst with Tinsel Town in terms of their unequivocal support he had at the start?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "his", "bubbles", "actually", "burst", "with", "Tinsel", "Town", "in", "terms", "of", "their", "unequivocal", "support", "he", "had", "at", "the", "start", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Ultimately, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Ultimately", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tinsel Town"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Los Angeles"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You think when push comes to shove?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "when", "push", "comes", "to", "shove", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "MITH: When push comes to shove, they have no trouble getting people to pay for those very expensive dinners and getting people to attend various events all over Los Angeles from different communities, I would say no.", "answer_tokens": ["MITH", ":", "When", "push", "comes", "to", "shove", ",", "they", "have", "no", "trouble", "getting", "people", "to", "pay", "for", "those", "very", "expensive", "dinners", "and", "getting", "people", "to", "attend", "various", "events", "all", "over", "Los", "Angeles", "from", "different", "communities", ",", "I", "would", "say", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "What do you do to try and deal with that tiny percentage who are unstable and blur those lines?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "to", "try", "and", "deal", "with", "that", "tiny", "percentage", "who", "are", "unstable", "and", "blur", "those", "lines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Look I think you raise some very interesting points and questions in the last segment.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "I", "think", "you", "raise", "some", "very", "interesting", "points", "and", "questions", "in", "the", "last", "segment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "How do you deal with changing people's minds?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "changing", "people", "'s", "minds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, again I think that one has to recognize how badly do we want to solve this problem.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", "I", "think", "that", "one", "has", "to", "recognize", "how", "badly", "do", "we", "want", "to", "solve", "this", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Lanza"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What do you say to other parents out there who might have concerns about their son, what should they do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "other", "parents", "out", "there", "who", "might", "have", "concerns", "about", "their", "son", ",", "what", "should", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Well, I happen to be very sympathetic to Mrs. Lanza because I know what it's like to deal with people who have developmental disabilities, who are periodically violent, who cannot be committed (ph) and what happens in some homes with parents who are struggling with children who had behavioral disorders even if they can get somebody or a doctor a young male is in denial of illness refuses to take medicine and there's enough of this climate of fear within the home that the illness ends up controlling the home.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "happen", "to", "be", "very", "sympathetic", "to", "Mrs.", "Lanza", "because", "I", "know", "what", "it", "'s", "like", "to", "deal", "with", "people", "who", "have", "developmental", "disabilities", ",", "who", "are", "periodically", "violent", ",", "who", "can", "not", "be", "committed", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "what", "happens", "in", "some", "homes", "with", "parents", "who", "are", "struggling", "with", "children", "who", "had", "behavioral", "disorders", "even", "if", "they", "can", "get", "somebody", "or", "a", "doctor", "a", "young", "male", "is", "in", "denial", "of", "illness", "refuses", "to", "take", "medicine", "and", "there", "'s", "enough", "of", "this", "climate", "of", "fear", "within", "the", "home", "that", "the", "illness", "ends", "up", "controlling", "the", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "OK, Michael?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "Michael", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I think we can get to the bottom of this with further scrutiny.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "can", "get", "to", "the", "bottom", "of", "this", "with", "further", "scrutiny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Is it with the AHA or is it with the studios or a bit of both?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "with", "the", "AHA", "or", "is", "it", "with", "the", "studios", "or", "a", "bit", "of", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "It's a bit of both.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "bit", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What kind of reaction have you had from the Hollywood industry?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "reaction", "have", "you", "had", "from", "the", "Hollywood", "industry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I think people are fairly shocked that this is going on that this monitor service is not what it claims to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "are", "fairly", "shocked", "that", "this", "is", "going", "on", "that", "this", "monitor", "service", "is", "not", "what", "it", "claims", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["MSNBC"], "PERSON": ["Martin Bashir", "Sarah Palin"]}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "You know, I think it damages him certainly in a short run, I think the question is, you know, obviously he has this political aspirations, what will that do for those or down the line?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "damages", "him", "certainly", "in", "a", "short", "run", ",", "I", "think", "the", "question", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "obviously", "he", "has", "this", "political", "aspirations", ",", "what", "will", "that", "do", "for", "those", "or", "down", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I mean, you made an interesting point and I thought which is that Martin Bashir who's a fellow Brit who's on air at MSNBC, he got into hot water of a comment he made attacking Sarah Palin over her analogy of slavery to modern day issues.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "made", "an", "interesting", "point", "and", "I", "thought", "which", "is", "that", "Martin", "Bashir", "who", "'s", "a", "fellow", "Brit", "who", "'s", "on", "air", "at", "MSNBC", ",", "he", "got", "into", "hot", "water", "of", "a", "comment", "he", "made", "attacking", "Sarah", "Palin", "over", "her", "analogy", "of", "slavery", "to", "modern", "day", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Can you draw that distinction?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "draw", "that", "distinction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "You know, I think that's an interesting point.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "an", "interesting", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Would you ever -- When you grew up from the streets, would you ever done something like that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "--", "When", "you", "grew", "up", "from", "the", "streets", ",", "would", "you", "ever", "done", "something", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]